Body's inside.
Victim's name is
Gabriel Meadows.
Somebody hit him in the back
of the head with a blunt object.
Cleaning crew found
him around 1:00 A.M.
Any witnesses?
Local boys talked to a
co-worker, Dave Bisping
who saw him here at
10:00 last night.
- Rigsby's meeting him at CBI.
- What about the murder weapon?
Nothing inside.
Maybe the killer
dropped it nearby.
Get a group of people together.
Search the area.
Trash duty.
- Is there a problem?
- No. Nothing.
Alright, when Cho
shows up, grab him.
- Spread the pain around.
- Alright.
[instrumental music]
Morning, Lisbon.
Is it morning yet?
Not quite.
Any prints?
None. But it looks
like someone wiped up.
Some of the blood is smears,
not spatter.
Was anything missing?
Looks like his
laptop was taken
but whoever took it
was in a hurry.
They left his cell
phone and wallet.
Interesting, yes?
Hmm, because the murder
and the theft
seem hurried, impulsive.
But the cleanup,
methodical and careful.
Almost as if it was carried out
by two different people.
You think somebody else
cleaned up after he was killed?
Why would somebody do that?
Excellent question.
"Anti-Cult activistnetwork."
I've heard of them,
they expose fake religions
rescue cult members,
stuff like that?
Meadows specialized
in one in particular.
"Visualize."
Wait, that's the cult
that Bret Stiles runs.
- You got it.
- Great. Great.
We're dealing with those wackos
again.
"Wackos?"
That's a little
uncharitable, Lisbon.
Uncharitable?
What do you mean?
Well, I always knew
that you were
closed-minded
about Visualize
but I never thought
you were actually bigoted.
I'm not bigoted.
Of course you
would think that.
Because your
preconceptions blind you.
'Use your eyes.'
Your eyes are
the gateway to truth.
I actually have no idea
what you're talking about.
I know you don't,
but he does. Hi.
Excuse me?
You're a member
of Visualize.
- No, I'm not.
- Yes, you are.
"Your eyes are
the gateway to truth.."
Visualize dogma.
You're the only one
that recognized it.
Look, I don't know
what you're after.
- I'm just trying to do my job.
- Well, let me explain.
A critic of Visualize
was killed here this evening
and a member shows
up at the scene.
That can't be an accident.
You're the one that
cleared all this up.
- Well, that's crazy.
- I don't think it's crazy.
- What's your name?
- Downs.
Were you involved in this,
Officer Downs?
No. No.
Liar, liar,
pants on fire.
You're coming with us.
We're gonna search your car.
- Stop him! Somebody stop him!
- Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Let me go!
- This is religious persecution!
- Let's go.
Pre-member bigot!
Sticks and stones
may break my bones
but names will never hurt me.
[theme music]
We're testing your
uniform for blood
and we found this in the trunk
of your squad car.
Your watch commander
vouched for your whereabouts
at the time of the murder.
We know you didn't
kill Meadows
but you did clean
up the crime scene
making it very difficult
for us to find the killer.
Why would you do that?
Hello?
So, Mr. Bisping, you set up
A-CAN with Meadows, right?
How'd he get into
the anti-cult business?
Uh, Gabe was born
into Visualize.
When his parents
died five years ago
he sort of woke up.
Um..
His younger sister
is still in Visualize.
Everything he did
was about getting her out.
All it did
was get him killed.
Visualize has
a lot of enemies.
Why would they target Gabe?
To shut him up.
Gabe was
a fierce researcher.
He broke a lot of
embarrassing stories
about Visualize
for our web site.
He was hitting
the inner circle hard.
The inner circle?
They help Stiles
run Visualize.
It-it's sort of his
College of Cardinals.
What was Gabe working
on before he died?
Murder.
From the early days
of Visualize back in the '70s.
Gabe thought Stiles
killed a rival of his
to consolidate his power.
He dig up any evidence?
He told me last
week he was close.
Now he's dead.
What do you think?
[telephone ringing]
How's the spy?
He hasn't moved since
we brought him in.
- It's creepy.
- Well, it's not surprising.
He's a member of
a brainwashing cult.
The thought of a clean mind
is terribly
frightening to you.
Isn't it, Patrick?
Bret Stiles.
The brainwasher-in-chief.
Ah, Agent Lisbon,
it's been far too long.
Why are you here,
Mr. Stiles?
I'm the spiritual advisor
of a man that you've imprisoned
and I was told
that Patrick here
tricked him into revealing
that he was a member
of my church
which, of course,
is not a crime.
He tampered with evidence.
That is a crime.
Well, if you let me
talk to him, Agent Lisbon
I'm sure we can clear
all this up.
Uh, what's going on, Bret?
- Hmm?
- They're not Visualize members.
They're professional muscle.
You don't trust your own
people to protect you.
What are you scared of?
I wouldn't want you
to mistake me
for Red John
and shoot me.
[intense music]
Look at me.
Tell them everything.
I heard a report of
the body over my radio.
Got to the office before
the first responders.
Wiped the surfaces
for fingerprints
wiped up some blood, too.
- Why?
- Meadows was an ex-member.
A non-person.
Whoever killed him was
doing Visualize a service.
You were duty-bound to
help clean up the evidence
weren't you?
No. I did it
of my own initiative.
You know, as a rule,
we hope to welcome back
'ex-members into the fold.'
We certainly don't want
to aid their assassins.
What about the missing laptop?
Did you take that?
No.
The computer was already
gone when I got there.
Hmm.
That's the truth.
[sighs]
Alright.
Take him to booking
Well, I've done
my good deed for the day.
If there's nothing else,
I'll be getting along.
We just have
a few more questions.
Well, uh, could we
do it on the walk?
Uh, I've gotta get back
to running my religion.
Yes, your flock
won't fleece itself.
Mr. Stiles, where were you last
night between 10:00 and 1:00?
What, uh, during the murder?
Let me see.
I was at Casper's Bistro.
Had the roasted turbot.
It was a little dry.
We'll check, I'm also gonna
have Agent Rigsby get in contact
with your people to see what
your schedule was yesterday.
Of course.
Uh, I have one last question.
You did this
for a lowly drone.
Why is that?
Every man in Visualize
is like a son to me.
Every woman
is my daughter.
Ooh. How are those
demons of yours
coming on, Patrick?
They're still chasing you,
are they?
I'm chasing them.
Are you?
Seriously, I haven't had
hot water in three days.
My landlord's being a total
jerk and won't fix it.
You should buy.
So I can deal with a bank
instead of a landlord?
Big step up.
Excuse me, agents?
We found something.
You should take a look.
They were stuffed
inside this old TV.
We almost missed 'em.
Ooh, a lot of blood here.
That suit
looks handmade.
If the tailor's local,
maybe we can ID the owner.
"Gerard's on Sutter."
- That's in San Fran, isn't it?
- Yeah.
What are you reading?
"Visualize Self."
You thinking about converting?
Yeah, just brushing up.
Well, Stiles might have to
write his next book from jail.
His alibi didn't hold up.
He left the restaurant
at 10:30.
- Well, that's not like him.
- To lie?
- No, to do it so poorly.
- Van Pelt and Cho called in.
Tailor identified the clothes.
They belong to Bret Stiles.
Alright, we're dealing with the
head of a multi-national cult
a 900-pound gorilla.
We need to proceed
carefully and slowly.
Put together a timeline
of the day of the murder.
I wanna know where
he was every minute.
- You got it.
- We should pay Bret a visit.
Not until we have
an airtight case.
Where's the fun in that?
Let's get a stick and go
and poke this 900-pound gorilla.
See what happens.
[instrumental music]
Mr. Stiles.
Oh, Patrick. Agent Lisbon.
How nice of you
to join us.
This is Cal Leben
and Jason Cooper.
Two of my most
loyal lieutenants.
Your alibi for the Meadows
killing didn't hold up.
You left that restaurant
hours earlier
than you told me you did.
Really? I must have been
mistaken. I'm sorry.
And, uh, we found bloody
clothes in a dumpster
'near the crime scene.'
Bloody clothes
that belong to you.
Listen, I give clothes
away all the time
to Visualize charities.
Yeah, I'm sure you do.
[phone ringing]
Would you excuse me?
Rigsby, what's up?
What's going on, Bret?
Beg your pardon?
You know this doesn't look good,
yet you're not asking
the questions that you should.
Huh?
Why is it that
you're not worried?
What does Bret Stiles
have to be worried about?
Well, he's about to get
arrested for murder.
- Bret, what's he talking about?
- Let it go.
- Do you recognize this?
- Well. Let me see. Ooh.
Well, I suppose it could
be me giving a speech.
Aha.
I give lots of speeches.
It was taken yesterday,
and you're wearing
the shirt and tie
we found covered in blood.
Bret Stiles,
you're under arrest
for the murder of
Gabriel Meadows.
You have to come with us.
Let's go.
I said let's go.
[chairs creaking]
[intense music]
[music continues]
Uh..
Everyone, no cause for alarm.
Be at peace.
- Thank you.
- Yes, sir.
[music continues]
Yes.
That appears to be mine.
Where did the blood
come from?
I don't know.
Meadows was writing an
article on Timothy Farragut.
He thought you'd
murdered him.
Poor old Tim.
He died, oh,
30 years ago now.
Car crash on PCH.
And what if Meadows
found evidence
that it wasn't an accident?
That would give you motive
for murder, wouldn't it?
No.
Because there's nothing to find.
Look, I'm not responsible
for Tim's death
or the demise
of Mr. Meadows.
Then why does the
evidence say you are?
Well, maybe
I'm being set up.
And why would
somebody do that?
Tell me, Agent Lisbon.
Do you enjoy watching
Patrick Jane
take over your team
and your life?
We close cases.
That's all that
matters to me.
Oh, I see.
So you're telling me that you
love justice more than yourself?
Come on.
Justice, what-what is that?
It's just an idea.
You are flesh and blood.
Why sacrifice the real
for the imaginary?
I'm not looking
for a guru.
- I'm looking for a murderer.
- Hmm.
Well..
...I didn't kill anybody.
And if you keep
insisting that I did then..
...gonna have to lawyer up.
[telephone ringing]
He's lawyered up.
It doesn't give us
much time to nail him.
Where are we at with
the bloody clothes?
Lab confirmed the blood type is
A-Negative, same as the victim
but they won't have the DNA
results for three or four days.
We don't have that much time.
We need something else.
We're still missing the murder
weapon and the victim's laptop.
We're gonna need to search
his house and office.
- I'll get a warrant.
- Good.
Where are we at with
the Farragut motive?
Well, apparently,
his notes were on the laptop
so that's no good.
I have a file of his stories.
Meadows definitely
had a solid contact
feeding him inside
information about Visualize.
Any idea on how
to find the source?
Yeah, there's an old hippie
named Randall Parker.
He's an ex-Visualize member.
Meadows talked to him last week.
Start with him.
What about Meadows' sister?
She's at Clear View ,
the Visualize College.
Visualize has a college?
Apparently, you major
in yourself.
Ah, Patrick.
I wondered when
you'd pop in.
Hmm.
Reading about you.
Gabe Meadows doesn't paint
a very pretty picture.
Oh, surely you're not going
to fall forgutter journalism.
One thing that's consistent
in all these stories
is that you never actually
wield the knife yourself.
You always manipulate someone
else into doing your dirty work.
That's somethingyou'd
know a little bit about.
Getting Red John to kill
the San Joaquin killer
that was very nice.
Almost elegant, I'd say.
Yes, you're coming along.
I'm doing nothing
of this sort.
You're not very happy,
are you, Patrick?
Perhaps you feel a bit like
the sorcerer's apprentice
you've woken up a power
that you can't control.
Tell me, how is
Rosalind Harker
enjoying life under
FBI protection?
Is she glad that you brought
Red John back into her life?
Are you enjoying this?
'Cause I know you didn't
kill Gabe Meadows.
I've been telling
you that all along.
But you're not acting like
a man that's being framed.
Even someone in your position
is gonna reach out for help
when being framed.
Jon Musashi.
I'm Mr. Stiles' attorney.
This interview is over.
Hi, Jon.
Are you a member of Visualize?
Yes, I think you are.
Did you know that Mr. Stiles'
last lawyer was a murderer?
Whereas I am not.
And again,
this interview is over.
Excellent.
Well, if you'll excuse me
always a pleasure.
Nice to meet you, Jon
Jon..
Thank you for coming.
- Thank you--
- Mr. Stiles, please.
[Stiles]
'I need to tell
them everything.'
'But I mean, you know me.'
I mean, I'm the leader
of a church, I mean..
[church bell ringing]
Really, I'm okay.
I'm glad to hear it.
No, I mean you can
go back to class.
Oh, my inner visions
don't start for another hour.
Agent Lisbon.
Dean Nora Hill.
Ah, thank you for taking
the time to meet me.
Happy to assist.
That will be all, Rose.
Thank you, Dean Hill.
Jessie Meadows is waiting
for you in Stiles Hall.
It's an impressive campus.
Thank you.
4,642 students
from 27 countries.
Only the best and
the brightest young people.
How are the students
taking the news?
What news?
That one of the students'
brother's been murdered
and your leader's been
arrested for the crime?
They don't know about that.
They don't need to.
But it's all over
the internet.
They don't have
The mind suffers from junk
food as much as the body does.
We keep it away.
Does Jessie know
her brother's dead?
Aren't you gonna
tell her?
[Lisbon]
'We'll do whatever we can
to find out who did this.'
I am so sorry
for your loss.
Oh, Gabe.
I'm sorry he's dead
but he wasn't a part
of my life anymore.
He's still your brother.
He left me.
Left us.
That's not what
a brother does.
Can you think of anybody
who may have wanted to hurt him?
Gabe published stories
about our community.
Some of the students here,
they didn't like it.
Some of them even thought that
I was feeding him information.
- Were you?
- No, I wouldn't do that.
I know you and your
brother didn't get along.
And he wanted to help you.
I think he wanted that
more than anything.
That was the problem.
I didn't need his help.
He couldn't see that.
I'm with my real family here.
[engine revving]
[Rigsby]
'Thanks for seeing me,
Mr. Parker.'
Meadows broke a lot of
stories about Visualize.
Were you his source?
All my stories are
30 years old.
All I know about
are the old days.
Did he ask you about
Timothy Farragut?
- Sure.
- What'd you tell him?
Well, Farragut
was into dispelling
all the bad vibes
in the world.
I liked how that sounded.
A lot of people did.
People who felt guilty
about having too much money.
When did Bret Stiles
come into the picture?
'76 or so.
A year later, Farragut died,
and Stiles wastheman.
I read the police report.
Farragut's death seems like
an open-and-shut
drunk driving fatality.
Well, you notice
who wrote that report.
Sheriff Elliott Elswit.
Oh, he liked those
Visualize ladies
and Stiles made sure
he met plenty.
So you're saying that
the sheriff doctored the report?
Well, Farragut didn't drink.
How'd he get so loaded
he couldn't see a tree?
How do I get in touch
with the sheriff?
Elswit's been
dead 20 years.
A suicide, they say.
And you think that Bret Stiles
killed him, too?
You bet I do.
- You think I'm crazy?
- No.
It's just a lot
of conspiracy talk.
Well, just because
you're paranoid
don't mean they're
not after you.
Hey.
Where are you?
- I'm back at the snake pit.
- Visualize? Why?
[Jane]
'Okay, so the Visualize
attorney shows up'
and Stiles starts acting
all weird and scared.
It's just like a little show.
- Hey, could you hold on?
- Yeah.
Uh, would you mind giving
me some privacy, please?
Really? Go.
So Stiles is acting scared.
So?
Well, it's for
the benefit of the lawyer.
Whatever game he's playing,
it isn't aimed at us.
It's aimed at Visualize,
and I'm here to find out why.
- I'll call you when I get out.
- 'Okay.'
Bye.
[instrumental music]
Leben.
Mr. Jane.
Hope the whole
"Arrest your master" thing
didn't ruin your lunch.
No hard feelings, right?
Did you come here to gloat?
No, I can gloat from a distance.
I have a message from Stiles.
- Hmm. What is it?
- Sorry.
It's for the entire
inner circle.
Ah, you can give it to me.
I'll pass it to
the other members.
Yeah, I-I don't think so.
I think I need the whole gang.
Light the Bret signal.
Gather the pooh-bahs.
Come on.
Let's go.
Ah..
Agent Grace Van Pelt,
I presume.
Mr. Stiles, I'm hoping you can
help me with something.
I'm trying to find
any property
held by you in the
state of California.
A car, a residence?
- Please, Agent Grace Van Pelt.
- Excuse me?
The helpless maiden routine?
Worth a try. Look, I can't
find anything you own.
Well, that's because
there's nothing to find.
I have no house, no car.
certainly not
in myname. Hmm?
I've dedicated my
life to Visualize.
So there's no place
for us to look?
Oh, no. You can look and look.
You will not find.
You're upset.
Something small, domestic?
A household problem?
No.
Hmm? But no, it's not family.
But still, it's...
connected to the home.
Landlord.
Petty dictator, no doubt.
Abuses you because he can.
Or because he's
a jerk. He won't fix..
You're good.
Not as good as Jane,
but good.
Hmm.
The anger that you
feel is a symptom
of a deeper condition
an organic rage, if you will.
'You know..'
I can help you with that.
Not interested.
Hmm?
Close your eyes.
Come on. Close your eyes.
Visualize your anger as
a red cloud inside your body.
Take some deep breaths.
Exhale.
Let the red smoke
come out of your body.
Try it.
Red smoke?
Seriously?
Or not.
Your choice.
[instrumental music]
[door screeching]
Mr. Jane, you have
a message for us from Bret?
Uh, no, not really, no.
Do you mind if I sit here?
Just can't resist.
Looks too comfortable.
Wow.
I don't understand.
We were told you had a message.
No, that was a lie.
I just wanted to get
you all together. Sorry.
Why did you need
to get in here?
Get the lay of the land see
who's running the show
now that Bret's in the clink.
None of us would presume to.
Bret Stiles is
still our leader.
Other members of the inner
circle are flying in.
We hold a vote
reaffirming Bret tomorrow.
Is that what you
came here to find out?
I came here to accuse one
of you of framing Bret Stiles
for the murder
of Gabriel Meadows.
[instrumental music]
And judging from your
reactions, none of you did that.
Of course we didn't.
Well, that clarifies
things considerably.
How?
Well, either one
of you framed Bret Stiles..
Or?
Or you didn't.
What does that mean?
Sorry. Can't tell you that.
That is a police secret.
But you're gonna love it
when you do find out.
Carry on.
[crickets chirping]
[Grace Van Pelt]
'You said you'd fix it.'
Do you have hot water
at your place?
Yeah, it's nice, isn't it?
Fine. Whatever.
[Grace gasping]
[soft music]
Hmm.
Well, what do you know?
[Rigsby]
'Farragut had a commune
called Visualize'
'down at Big Sur
in the mid '70s.'
'Just a few hundred members'
and a promising young
guru named Bret Stiles.
Farragut crashes his car.
Stiles takes over.
Now, the police report says
it was an accident.
Randal Parker says no,
Stiles killed Farragut
and the cop that made
the accident report
and Meadows, who was
investigating the whole thing.
That's crazy.
I don't know. I wouldn't
put anything past Stiles.
Well, one thing's
for certain. We can't prove it.
But Meadows may have a source
inside Visualize who can.
- Any idea who that source is?
- No.
It's definitely not
the sister. Who else is there?
Maybe Stiles knows.
I could ask. He talked
to me earlier.
Maybe I could get
him to open up.
What'd he say?
He showed me something.
Never mind. It's nothing.
He's trying to get to you.
What?
No.
Okay. Take another run
at him, but be careful.
Alright.
Hello, Grace.
You look refreshed.
You tried my little trick then.
No.
Works though, doesn't it?
I wanted to ask you
about Timothy Farragut.
He ran Visualize
before you did, right?
No one ran Visualize
before I did.
No one.
Hmm.
Tim said things that
people wanted to hear
but he didn't know what to do
with the people who listened.
What do you mean?
[sighs]
Farragut was a dreamer.
And dreamers are
useful in their way
but we don't live
in dreams, do we?
We live in the here
and the now.
Did you kill him?
You've killed, haven't you?
Someone who mattered
to you, who hurt you.
Did you enjoy it?
- No.
- Really?
I'm told it gives the feeling
of great perspective
like waking from a dream.
It...it changes you.
Did your friends notice?
A little.
But I think
it freaks 'em out.
Of course. They don't
have the imagination
orthe vocabulary to converse
with you about it. Hmm.
You know..
...you're like a little
bird that fell out of a nest
but you don't need the nest.
You need to fly..
...and that..
...I can teach you.
[Lisbon]
'How was your trip
to Visualize?'
Enlightening. I need a
little more information.
Could Bret Stiles know what
blood type Meadows was?
Sure. Visualize keeps medical
records on all its members.
And the source for Meadows'
stories was highly placed?
Way high.
Great.
Do you know
who the killer is?
Better. I know
how to catch them.
We need Stiles' lawyer in here
first thing in the morning.
Did you get anything
from Stiles?
No. He's not saying anything.
Van Pelt, you know how
to do that computer
picture makeover thing?
You mean Photoshop?
Yeah. We got
a lot of work to do.
On what?
Manufacturing evidence,
of course.
[instrumental music]
One of our people was
canvassing the neighborhood
and noticed a
traffic light camera
across from the A-CAN building.
We blew up an image
and hit pay dirt.
That looks like blood
to me. What do you think?
Mr. Stiles?
Bret?
Meadows got evidence
that you killed Farragut.
That's what was
on his computer.
So you killed him
and stole it.
But it was the cover-up
that got you.
We're filing charges
against your client
and booking him immediately.
I'll stay with him, of course.
It's alright, Jon. Bye.
- But, Bret, I think--
- Jon.
[intense music]
A phony photograph, Patrick?
Worth a thousand lies.
So you've stooped
to framing me now?
Well, you framed yourself first.
Well. That's true. I did.
But you never
believed it anyway.
Well, I didn't think
you were that stupid
unless, of course, you
were doing it on purpose.
Ah. It was a pity.
One of my better suits.
Shame to have to ruin
it like that.
Where'd you get the blood?
Oh, I have my sources.
The DNA won't match,
of course, but by the time
that comes to light, I'll
know what I need to know.
Which is which one
of the inner circle
wanted to take your place.
Well, it's best
to smoke out your rivals
before they get too strong.
I appeared weak
because I wanted to see
who would reach for the crown.
- Who did?
- No one.
You overestimated the courage
of your bootlickers.
They're all too scared
to make a move.
Oh. That'swhy you doctored up
that ridiculous photograph.
Well, I figured if they
wanted to cook your goose
a little better, I'd turn
up the heat for them.
Well, thank you, Patrick.
I didn't know you cared.
I don't.
I did it to catch
the killer. You coming?
- Where are we going?
- Crash the party.
Oh, I love a party.
I nominate Jason Cooper
to assume all roles and
duties as head of Visualize.
I second the motion.
Then we vote. I vote "aye."
Well, I will not
allow false modesty
to tarnish the moment.
Aye.
Nay.
Bret Stiles isand always will
be the leader of Visualize.
Nay.
Aye.
[people applauding]
Uh, I'm sorry. Are we
interrupting something?
Bret, you're free.
We dropped the charges.
Looks like you guys
have been busy.
Hello, Cooper.
I see you've taken the seat
at the head of the table.
That's very bold of you.
We thought..
What? You thought, what?
My corpse cold enough to loot?
Bret.
Mr. Stiles..
Do you really think that I am
weak enough to be pushed aside?
I mean, do-do you think
that I'm stupid enough
to get caught
with blood on my hands?
Tell me, Cooper.
Do I seem weak to you now?
Hmm?
Sit down.
[people applauding]
Thank you.
Nice to be back.
Just one more piece
of business to, uh, clear up.
In the matter
of personal curiosity
who of you voted
for Cooper here?
Hmm?
Well, I don't see
how that's important.
Well, that's one vote,
Obviously. Who else
voted for Cooper?
You did.
And you.
'Yes, and you.'
Oh, Bret, looks like
it was a landslide.
Well, Leben.
You've always been
true to me, I know.
Hmm.
I see.
I stood by you, Bret.
I told them they were
fools to doubt you.
Really?
Stiles is going down for murder.
Shouldn't you have sucked
up to the new boss
'like the rest of these folks?'
The bloody clothes,
the security footage
'Stiles seemed very guilty.'
You had to be 100%
sure he wasn't.
How would you know that?
You're the killer.
That's ridiculous.
- Hmm.
- Is it?
[Lisbon]
'You couldn't warn the others'
'because then they would
know you were a murderer.'
You voted for Stiles because
you knew he'd be coming back.
[intense music]
Damn you for what
you've turned me into.
So you were Meadows'
inside source?
I fed him information
when it helped me.
You leaked stories that hurt
your enemies at Visualize.
My mistake was..
...was letting him
know who I was.
Meadows was desperate
to connect Stiles
to the murder of Farragut
and he thought I knew
something that could prove it.
Why not give it to him?
Doesn't exist.
Do you think Bret Stiles
needs a smoking gun?
He probably didkill
Farragut and that sheriff
but there'll never be
any evidence to prove it.
I don't believe you.
That's the truth.
What do you think Stiles
would do if he found out
you'd been feeding
me information?
[Nora Hill]
I sensed that Meadows' crusade
was pushing him
to desperate measures.
So...I brought the
hammer, just in case.
I knew my name was all over
the laptop, so I took it.
I examined myself honestly
and I find I feel no remorse.
150,000 people die
every single day.
And why should I feel anything
for one man, just 'cause..
...just 'cause I was
the cause of his death?
That's a good question.
Sign here.
So that's it then.
Thank you for letting
me watch this.
No problem.
Visualizing my anger
works really well.
Just returning the favor.
There's so much more
that I could teach you.
Is there?
To be free of doubt,
anger, fear.
Let me show you the world
as you've never seen it.
Let me show you
you as you've never
seen yourself.
Great sales pitch.
But I'm sort of over
bad boys these days.
Thanks anyway.
Ms. Hill killed Gabe? Why?
There was political
stuff going on.
But I think mostly your brother
just wanted you to be happy
and to get out.
I don't know what to do.
We were going through
your brother's laptop
and we found some videos
that he'd made for you.
Kinda like letters.
I thought you might
like to see one.
'Happy Birthday, sis.'
I hope it's a good one.
I don't know if you'll
ever see this
but I just wanted to say
that I'm proud of you.
'I miss you so much, sis.'
'I know we don't agree
about some things'
but, uh, I hope you know
that I'm always here for you.'
Anytime.
I'll be waiting.
'See you soon, I hope.'
Are there more of these?
Yeah, there's a whole
lot of 'em.
Would it be okay if I
stayed to watch a few?
You can stay as
long as you'd like.
Ah, Patrick.
Always a pleasure
doing business with you.
There are many fearful men
hiding from my wrath tonight.
It's a good feeling
And the murder of Farragut goes
back in the cold case file
so that's a nice twofer.
Well, you didn't do
toobadly yourself.
You played a deep
game here, Patrick.
A mind like yours could've
developed a dozen ways
of tricking Nora Hill
without helping me
in mylittle power play.
Well, I'm flattered.
It was the easiest way.
No.
You wanted me to owe you
a favor, didn't you?
Hmm? Well, alright.
I owe you.
Yes.
You do.
Goodnight.
[instrumental music]